Finally, we want to make recommendations.
最后 我们将做出推荐
The whole idea is that, we want to make
对于之前没有通过基于协同过滤的推荐机制
content-based recommendations for the individuals
获得推荐电影的用户
who didn't have collaborative filtering-based recommendations before.
我们将通过基于内容的推荐机制向他们推荐电影
Now, just following the comments here for user and users.
我们按照这些注释编写代码
For each user, update the progress bar.
对于每个用户 更新进度条
So, the counter's going to go up by one.
计数器将加一
Update that. So then,
更新进度条然后
we're going to pull only the reviews that the user has seen.
仅提取用户看过的电影的评价
So, if you remember,
如果你还记得的话
this ranked_reviews is a DataFrame that we created that basically is ordered by
这个 ranked_reviews 是我们创建的一个 DataFrame
the movies that the user has seen and for each user from highest to lowest ranking,
它根据用户看过的电影排序 对于每个用户
this DataFrame sort of shows the movies that they've seen.
这个 DataFrame 都从高到低地显示他们看过的电影
I'm just going to call this temp.
我将称之为 temp
So, we're going to do that, we're going to look at
我将查看从高到低排序的
each of the movies from highest to lowest.
每部电影
So, I'm going to just create an array of the movie ID,
创建一个包含 movie_id 的数组
and then what we want to do is we want to pull the movie names.
然后提取电影片名
So, movie_names, and we're
movie_names...
going to use the get_movie_names function that we wrote up there.
我们将使用在上面编写的 get_movie_names() 函数
I'm going to pass in the movie_ids.
传入 movie_ids
Then finally, what we want to do,
最后
is we want to find similar movies,
我们想要查找相似电影
so we wrote this.
我们编写了这个函数
The part that we wrote was to find similar movies to that
这部分会查找相似的电影
basically for the movies that the user has seen and they've ranked high,
用户看过这些电影 并且排名很高
we want to pull other similar movies and recommend those movies to the user.
我们想要提取其他相似的电影并推荐给用户
So, for movie in movie.
for movie in movie_ids:
So we're going to pull the movie ID,
我们将提取 movie_id
we're going to get the most similar ones,
并获取最相似的电影
we'll store that in rec_movies,
存储到 rec_movies 中
and then we'll take the difference between the movies that they've already
然后查看用户已经看过的电影
seen and the new movies that we're recommending to them.
与要推荐的新电影之间的差异
We don't want to recommend the movies that they've already seen still,
我们不想推荐用户已经看过的电影
and then basically what we'll do is we'll
我们将获取
take the original recommendations that were given to this user,
原来推荐给此用户的电影
and we're going to add these new recommendations
然后将通过基于内容的推荐机制
based on content-based recommendations to those recs.
获取的新电影添加到此 recs 中
So, they have a bunch of recommendations from the collaborative filtering based method.
他们已经通过协同过滤方法获得了很多推荐电影
Now, we're basically going to update
现在我们将更新
that collaborative filtering-based recommendation
通过协同过滤方法推荐的电影列表
with some additional content-based recommendations, where possible.
并添加一些其他基于内容的推荐电影
Again, we'll say, if the length of the recommendations for that user exceeds nine, right.
如果该用户的 recs 长度超过 9
If we have 10 or more recommendations,
即有 10 部或以上的推荐电影
then we'll just break for that user.
那么我们将 break 出来
Yeah. So, we're going to break for that user,
是的我们将退出循环
and so that'll go out of this and then go and grab the next user,
并获取下个用户
right that's just breaking from making content.
这个 break
This break is only breaking from making content-based recommendations.
只是退出基于内容的推荐方式
So, one potential solution looks like,
这只是其中一种实现方法
there are multiple ways that you could do this.
还有很多其他实现方法
Again, this is sort of like taking those recommendations for each user,
我获取了每个用户的推荐电影列表
and updating the collaborative filtering-based recommendations
并用基于内容的推荐电影
with content-based recommendations.
更新基于协同过滤的推荐电影
I got an error. Users wasn't defined what'll I call this up here.
我出现了一个错误users 在这里没有定义
Technically, I have this as just like users who need recs.
这些是需要推荐的用户
So, if the users already have recommendations,
如果用户已经有推荐电影
then we're not going to make more recommendations for them.
那么我们不再向他们推荐更多电影
So, I'm just going to say, do this for just the users who need recommendations,
所以修改下这里 表示仅针对需要推荐的用户推荐电影
go through them and do this process.
遍历这些用户并执行此流程
This one's pretty fast.
这个运行很快